Thomas S. Power Papers
Thomas S. Power Papers
- Audiovisual material
  - Tapes
    - Washington Report of the Air, for December 16 - December 20, 1968; power_ts_0041; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For December 16 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Intellectual Ferment in Russia; Tape 2, For December 17 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Power of Poets in Russia Today; Tape 3, For December 18 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - A Yugoslav Poet’s Protest; Tape 4, For December 19 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Rationale Puts NATO on Alert; Tape 5, For December 20 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - The Domino Fact: Shaky Southeast Asia. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for December 23 - December 27, 1968; power_ts_0042; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For December 23 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Threat to Mid East Peace; Tape 2, For December 24 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar A. Mowrer - Fallacy of Building Bridges to Reds; Tape 3, For December 25 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Philippines: A Potential Asian Cuba; Tape 4, For December 26 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar A. Mowrer - How to Undermine Red Tyranny; Tape 5, For December 27 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - What Peking Seeks in Warsaw Talks. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for December 30 - January 3, 1968; power_ts_0043; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For December 30 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Budgeting for Military Superiority; Tape 2, For December 31 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - New Year’s Eve - Time of Hopes and Fears; Tape 3, For January 1 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Frank Johnson - Soviet Interest in the Suez Canal; Tape 4, For January 2 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - U.N. Irresponsibility; Tape 5, For January 3 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Washington’s Statements Hurt Saigon’s Prospects. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for January 6 - January 10, 1969; power_ts_0044; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For January 6 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Presses Claim to Control Mediterranean; Tape 2, For January 7 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Guyana Versus Communism: The People Win; Tape 3, For January 8 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Unstable Latin America; Tape 4, For January 9 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - East-West German Bridge-Building; Tape 5, For January 10 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Reorganization of Soviet Secret Police. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for January 13 - January 17, 1969; power_ts_0045; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For January 13 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with Amb. Ong - Fears for Peace in Vietnam; Tape 2, For January 14 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Henry Kissinger on Vietnam; Tape 3, For January 15 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Tibet Deserves "Conscience of Mankind"; Tape 4, For January 16 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Red Chinese Build-Up in Central Asia; Tape 5, For January 17 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with Amb. Ong - Malaysia’s New Red Uprising. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for January 20 - January 24, 1969; power_ts_0046; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For January 20 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The "Finlandization" of West Germany; Tape 2, For January 21 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar A. Mowrer - Italy in Trouble; Tape 3, For January 22 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Guerrilla War Growing in Thailand; Tape 4, For January 23 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Amb. Tan Sri Ong - Malaysia’s Attraction for Reds; Tape 5, For January 24 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Carlos Romulo Speaks for the Philippines. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for January 27 - January 31, 1969; power_ts_0047; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For January 27 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Cyprus: New Issue for Soviet Propaganda; Tape 2, For January 28 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Robert F. Turner - Vietnam Misgivings; Tape 3, For January 29 (Wednesday) Dr. Judd - Red China’s New Campaign Against Us; Tape 4, For January 30 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Robert F. Turner - What a Viet Cong Victory Might Mean; Tape 5, For January 31 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Dictatorship in Brazil. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for February 3 - February 7, 1969; power_ts_0048; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For February 3 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with Robert F. Turner - Threat of Red Victory and Purges in Vietnam; Tape 2, For February 4 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Diplomatic Moves in the Middle East; Tape 3, For February 5 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar A. Mowrer - Czechoslovakia Today; Tape 4, For February 6 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Chinese Red Pot Calls U.S. Kettle Black; Tape 5, For February 7 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with Robert F. Turner - How Reds View Peace Talks in Vietnam. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for February 10 - February 14, 1969; power_ts_0049; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For February 10 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Establishing Nuclear Center in Cuba; Tape 2, For February 11 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Odell Lee - What Vietnamese People Want; Tape 3, For February 12 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - New Soviet Propaganda Attack on Yugoslavia; Tape 4, For February 13 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Odell Lee - Strength of Vietnamese People; Tape 5, For February 14 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Moscow Explains Role of Satellites. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for February 17 - February 21, 1969; power_ts_0050; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For February 17 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Renewed Assault on Thailand; Tape 2, For February 18 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Odell Lee - Vietnamese Villagers’ View of Americans; Tape 3, For February 19 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Laotian Highway Penetration; Tape 4, For February 20 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Odell Lee - Black American’s View of War in Vietnam; Tape 5, For February 21 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Uruguay: Victim of Red Aggression. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for February 24 - February 28, 1969; power_ts_0051; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For February 24 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The Next Moves in Vietnam; Tape 2, For February 25 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Seek Spanish Port Facilities; Tape 3, For February 26 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Edgar A. Mowrer - Italy’s Recognition of Red China; Tape 4, For February 27 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Rebirth of Stalin as Soviet Hero; Tape 5, For February 28 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Death of an African Terrorist Leader. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for March 3 - March 7, 1969; power_ts_0052; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For March 3 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - New Communist Guerilla Move in Bolivia; Tape 2, For March 4 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Fails to Understand North Korea; Tape 3, For March 5 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Aim for Middle East Oil; Tape 4, For March 6 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with john F. Lewis - Iraq: Middle East Time Bomb; Tape 5, For March 7 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Laos Bombing Now Critical in Southeast Asia Situation. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for March 10 - March 14, 1969; power_ts_0053; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 22)
      Tape 1, For March 10 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Communist Pressure on Berlin; Tape 2, For March 11 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Undesirable Alternatives in the Middle East; Tape 3, For March 12 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Ceausecu and Longo Criticize the Kremlin; Tape 4, For March 13 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Reds Win Crucial Election in West Bengal; Tape 5, For March 14 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Political Play in Middle East. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for March 17 - March 21, 1969; power_ts_0054; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For March 17 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - New Soviet Military Developments; Tape 2, For March 18 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Frank Johnson - What Motivates the Russians; Tape 3, For March 19 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Protest the Policage of "Linkage"; Tape 4, For March 20 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Odell Lee - North Vietnamese Blunder in South Vietnam; Tape 5, For March 21 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Behind Sweden’s Swing to the Left. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for March 24 - March 28, 1969; power_ts_0055; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For March 24 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with Amb. Sudjatmoko - Indonesian Comeback; Tape 2, For March 25 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Israel’s Communists Help Arab Claims; Tape 3, March 26 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Amb. Sudjatmoko - Southeast Asian Cooperation; Tape 4, For March 27 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Peking’s Trade Penetration of Asia; Tape 5, For March 26 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with Amb. Sudjatmoko - Foreign Investment for Indonesia. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for March 31 - April 4, 1969; power_ts_0056; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For March 31 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The Soviet Purpose in Talks with the United States; Tape 2, For April 1 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Increase Influence in Arabian Peninsula; Tape 3, For April 2 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Slander U.S. in India; Tape 4, For April 3 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Berlin Cruch to Continue; Tape 5, For April 4 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Soviets Reiterate Right of Intervention. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 7 - April 11, 1969; power_ts_0057; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For April 7 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet First-Strike Threat; Tape 2, For April 8 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - South Africa Fears Red Chinese; Tape 3, For April 9 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - South Africa Prepares Indian Ocean Defenses; Tape 4, For April 10 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Zambia’s Internal Breakdown; Tape 5, For April 11 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Toothless British Lion. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 14 - April 18, 1969; power_ts_0058; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For April 14 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Russia’s "Pro" ABM System; Tape 2, For April 15 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Cuba’s Red Embassy in South Vietnam; Tape 3, For April 16 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - African Terrorism; Tape 4, For April 17 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - New Red Empire in Asia; Tape 5, For April 18 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - New Hope for Free Asians. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 21 - April 25, 1969; power_ts_0059; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For April 21 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - General Giap Unmasked; Tape 2, For April 22 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - What is Provacative in ABM; Tape 3, For April 23 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Terrorism Today in Portuguese Africa; Tape 4, For April 24 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Red China Rewrote the Rules; Tape 5, For April 25 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Giap’s Claim of America’s Defeat. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for April 28 - May 2, 1969; power_ts_0060; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For April 28 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Russian Anti-Space Defense; Tape 2, For April 29 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. Edward Teller - Costs: Defense Versus Offense; Tape 3, For April 30 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. Edward Teller - Will an ABM System Work?; Tape 4, For May 1 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. Edward Teller - The Fate of an Assured Deterrence; Tape 5, For May 2 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Giap Demands Total Victory. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for May 5 - May 9, 1969; power_ts_0061; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For May 5 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Leadership Lack Threatens Free World; Tape 2, For May 6 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. John Wheeler - ABM Needed to Protect Morale; Tape 3, For May 7 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Warsaw Pact Reorganization; Tape 4, For May 6 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Dr. John Wheeler - How Offensive is an ABM Defense?; Tape 5, For May 9 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Military Games, 1969. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for May 12 - May 16, 1969; power_ts_0062; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For May 12 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - ABM: Weapon Against War; Tape 2, For May 13 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Military Capability; Tape 3, For May 14 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Nuclear War "Inevitability" in Kremlin Mind; Tape 4, For May 15 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Opposition Arguments to ABM; Tape 5, For May 16 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Loses Superiority at Sea. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for May 19 - May 23, 1969; power_ts_0063; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For May 19 (Monday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Special ABM Study; Tape 2, For May 20 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Systemic Conflict; Tape 3, For May 21 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Objectives in the Cold War; Tape 4, For May 22 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Wartime Economy of U.S.S.R.; Tape 5, For May 23 (Friday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Soviet Education Lead. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for May 26 - May 30, 1969; power_ts_0064; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For May 26 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Lin Piao’s Moment of Victory; Tape 2, For May 27 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - The Error of Mao According to Lin Piao; Tape 3, For May 28 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - South Africa: America’s Friend; Tape 4, For May 29 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - South Atlantic Invitation to Soviets; Tape 5, For May 30 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - The Mystery of the Soviet Generals. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 2 - June 6, 1969; power_ts_0065; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For June 2 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet ICBM Construction Rate Increasing; Tape 2, For June 3 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - New Terror in Africa; Tape 3, For June 4 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Africa’s Red Training Camps; Tape 4, For June 5 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - African Insurgency Knows Little Success; Tape 5, For June 6 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Offensive Against NATO. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 9 - June 13, 1969; power_ts_0066; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For June 9 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - The Soviet Game In The Middle East; Tape 2, For June 10 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - Peking Inspires Malaysian Unrest; Tape 3, For June 11 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Leftist Threat to U.S. Business; Tape 4, For June 12 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - The Soviet Gambit In The Mediterranean; Tape 5, For June 13 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Czechoslavakia, The Complete Slave. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 16 - June 20, 1969; power_ts_0067; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 23)
      Tape 1, For June 16 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Behind World Revolution: Politics, Not Economics; Tape 2, For June 17 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Hits Cambodian Bases; Tape 3, For June 18 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Objectives in Red China; Tape 4, For June 19 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd - Operation Vesna, Soviet Spring Maneuvering; Tape 5, For June 20 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Military Industrial Complex. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 23 - June 27, 1969; power_ts_0068; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For June 23 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Singapore’s Financial Showdown with Peking; Tape 2, For June 24 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Podgorny’s Visit to North Korea; Tape 3, For June 25 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Red China’s Education System in Ruins; Tape 4, For June 26 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - New Soviet MIRV Testing; Tape 5, For June 27 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Thailand Holds Its Breath. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for June 30 - July 4, 1969; power_ts_0069; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For June 30 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Aircraft Industry Complex; Tape 2, For July 1 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Raymond Joseph - Haitian Powder Keg; Tape 3, For July 2 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - U.S. Industry: Victim of U.S. African Policy; Tape 4, For July 3 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Raymond Joseph - Haitian Coalition of Hope; Tape 5, For July 4 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - Secretary Laird Provides New Information on the Soviet Strategic Threat. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 7 - July 11, 1969; power_ts_0070; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For July 7 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Secretary Laird Provides New Information on the Chinese Communist Strategic Threat; Tape 2, For July 8 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with Raymond Joseph - Communists Inside Haiti; Tape 3, For July 9 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Soviet Connivance in Pueblo Seizure; Tape 4, For July 10 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with Raymond Joseph - Castro’s Threat to Haiti; Tape 5, For July 11 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - "Viva" Means Life for U.S. Colleges. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 14 - July 18, 1969; power_ts_0071; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)
      Tape 1, For July 14 (Monday) - Dr. Judd - Much Ado About Nothing; Tape 2, For July 15 (Tuesday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - SDS Convention Splits Markist Group; Tape 3, For July 16 (Wednesday) - Dr. Judd - Did Castro Jump The Gun in Vietnam?; Tape 4, For July 17 (Thursday) - Dr. Judd interview with John F. Lewis - Russia’s Involvement in Nigeria; Tape 5, For July 18 (Friday) - Dr. Judd - The ABM and Arms Control. The credit line at the end of each program fulfills the requirements of the broadcasting industry to identify the underwriter of public service programming on the air.
    - Washington Report of the Air, for July 21 - July 25, 1969; power_ts_0072; 1/4 inch audio tape; 1 reel; running time 3:15 (Box 24)